flutter a UI framework for building apps on iOS Android the web and desktop at
Flutter 一个用于在 iOS 上构建应用程序的 UI 框架Android Web 和桌面
its core flutter combines a high performance graphics engine with the
的核心 Flutter 在开发中结合了高性能图形引擎和
dart programming language in development dart provides full type safety and
dart 编程语言dart 提供完整的类型安全和
stateful hot reload to help you build reliable apps quickly in production dart
有状态的热重载，以帮助您在生产中快速构建可靠的应用程序 dart
compiles to native machine code which means your graphics will render
编译为本地机器代码，这意味着您的图形将
beautifully on any platform install flutter then run flutter create to
在任何平台上呈现精美安装flutter然后运行flutter create
create a new project now open the main dart file this is where you build your
创建一个新项目现在打开主dart文件这是您构建
app the UI is laid out as a tree of widgets and the framework provides
应用程序的地方UI被布置为小部件树和 该框架提供了
hundreds of pre-built widgets to handle things like animations scrolling
数百个预构建的小部件来处理诸如动画滚动
responsive layout and more you can build your own widget by extending the
响应布局之类的事情，您可以通过扩展
stateless widget class you then define your UI by overriding its build method
无状态小部件类来构建自己的小部件，然后通过覆盖其构建方法来定义您的 UI
now it's important to understand that everything in flutter is a widget this
现在重要的是要了解一切都在颤动 是一个小部件，此
method returns a widget and it's children return widgets and their
方法返回一个小部件，它的孩子返回小部件，他们的
children return widgets giving us an expressive declarative UI structure
孩子重新 turn 小部件为我们提供了一个富有表现力的声明式 UI 结构
which you can easily Traverse using flutters awesome tool whenever the input
，您可以使用 Flutters 轻松遍历，每当
data to this widget changes flutter will rebuild the UI by calling your build
此小部件的输入数据发生变化时，flutter 将通过调用您的构建方法重建 UI
method stateless widgets are immutable and don't have any internal data when
无状态小部件是不可变的，并且在您使用时没有任何内部数据
you have an interactive widgets where the internal data might change based on
有一个交互式小部件，其中内部数据可能会根据
user input you can extend a stateful widget properties defined on this class
用户输入而更改您可以扩展在此类上定义的有状态小部件属性
can be reactive for example we might have a counter that starts at zero then
可以是反应性的，例如我们可能有一个从零开始的计数器然后
in our build method we have one of flutters built-in buttons that cause a
在我们的构建方法中我们构建了一个颤振 -in 按钮会在
function whenever it's pressed it increments the counter by coin set state
按下时触发功能，它会通过硬币设置状态增加计数器，
which tells the framework that the widgets data has changed causing the UI
这会告诉框架小部件数据已更改，导致
to re-render with the latest data you can now play with this app on a real
UI 使用最新数据重新呈现，您现在可以在真实设备上使用此应用程序播放
device using the flutter run command that's cool and all but let's make some
使用很酷的颤振运行命令，但让我们进行一些
changes we'll go back to our source code and Center the button on the middle of
更改，我们将返回到我们的源代码并将中间的按钮居中
the screen instead of writing code just click on the button and hit control
屏幕的 dle 而不是编写代码只需单击按钮并点击 control
shift R then wrap your button with a center widget next change the color of
shift R 然后用中心小部件包裹您的按钮接下来更改
the button and notice how flutter previews that color directly in your IDE
按钮的颜色并注意颤振如何直接在您的 IDE 中预览该颜色
now too hot reload the app simply type or into the command line it only took a
现在太热了重新加载应用程序 只需在命令行中输入或输入，只需
few milliseconds to build a new version of our app and notice how the state of
几毫秒即可构建我们的应用程序的新版本，并注意
the counter was unchanged that's what I like to call an awesome developer
计数器的状态如何保持不变，这就是我喜欢称之为很棒的开发人员
experience this has been flutter in 100 seconds if you want to learn more check
体验 如果你在 100秒内颤动 想了解更多信息，请
out my newly updated flutter fire based course on fire ship i/o thanks for
查看我最近更新的关于 Fire Ship i/o 的基于 Flutter Fire 的课程 感谢
watching and I will see you in the next one
收看，我们下期再见
you